hiphoplead.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy - HipHopLead.com

HipHopLead.com (“HipHop Lead Media”) owns and operates this website (the “Site”). HipHop Lead Media may, from time to time, also deliver advertising to websites owned by third-party publishers that are not part of the HipHop Lead Media Network (“Non-Affiliated Sites”). This Privacy and Security Policy applies to (i) the collection of information on HipHop Lead Media Site that link to or display this Privacy and Security Policy and the use of that information, (ii) the collection of information on the Affiliated Sites and the use of that information when you view ads from our advertisers, and (iii) the collection of information on the Non-Affiliated Sites and the use of that information when you view ads from our advertisers.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or contact us, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

_To send periodic emails_  
The email address you provide, will only be used to send you information and updates. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Opt-Out Cookies (NAI)**  
To learn more about how our opt-out process works, please visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses (such as site’s traffic).

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer links to third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.hiphoplead.com/disclaimer/>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on October 2007

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

HipHop Lead Media  
Via Del Nespolo 13D  
San Giovanni In Croce, CR 26037  
Italy  
contact@hiphoplead.com  
+393409777445
